*****************************
	Basic Rules:
-Your hand will have ten cards
-When drawing, you can select from the deck
 or the top card from the discard pile
-Once you draw a card, one card from your
 hand must be discarded.
   -Note: it may be the drawn card
-Aces are low

	Objective:
-To get a run or a set of cards
-A run is comprised of at least three cards in
 numerical order of the same suit.
-A set is comprised of at least three cards of
 the same value.
-Deadwood: these are the cards that are not in
 a set or run
-Knocking: this is when you go out. Your 
 Deadwood must total ten or fewer points.
   -Note: facecards are worth ten points,
	  everything else is face value
-Going Gin: knocking when your Deadwood is
 worth zero points