Basic Rules:
************************************************************************
-Your hand will have ten cards
-When drawing, you can select the top card from the deck or discard pile
-Once a card is drawn, one card from your hand must be discarded.
   -Note: it may be the drawn card\n-Aces are low, worth one point
-Face cards are worth ten points\n-The game is composed of rounds
-You are trying to get to 50 points before the other player
-The starting player will alternate each round
************************************************************************
Press Enter to continue:

Common Terms:
************************************************************************
-Meld: a run or set.
-Run: comprised of at least three cards in numerical order of the same suit.
-Set: comprised of three or four cards of the same value.
-Deadwood: cards that are not in a meld. Your deadwood score is the face value 
           of the cards in your deadwood. Aces are 1 point, faces cards are 10
-Knocking: going out when your deadwood is worth 10 or fewer points
-Going Gin: knocking when your deadwood is worth zero points.
            When all of your cards are in melds
************************************************************************
Press Enter to continue:

Objective:
************************************************************************
-Get to 50 points before the other player.
-Get your cards into runs and/or sets and then knocking or declaring Gin.
-You may knock when your deadwood is worth ten or fewer points.
-The other player, known as the defending player, may \"lay off\" their deadwood.
-Laying Off: defender may add to the knocker's melds.
	-I.E. continue a run or add to a set
-The defender cannot lay off cards if the other player has declared Gin
************************************************************************
Press Enter to continue:

Points:
************************************************************************
-Points are based on the difference of Deadwood.
-The Deadwood value of the knocking player is subtracted from the defender's Deadwood
-The difference is then the points for that round
-Going Gin: gives a bonus of 25 points
-Undercutting: when the defender's Deadwood is less or equal to the knocking player's
	-Note: this can occour after laying off
-This is worth 25 points + the difference in Deadwood after laying off
************************************************************************
Press Enter to continue:
